{
    "subject": "David_Dhawan",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Taaqatwar",
    "human_readable": "David Dhawan directed the film Taaqatwar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9185054898262024,
            "question": "Who directed the film Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8606799840927124,
            "question": "Name a film directed by David Dhawan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8030811548233032,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by David Dhawan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6709878444671631,
            "question": "What year was the film Taaqatwar released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6122917532920837,
            "question": "How popular was the film Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5804613828659058,
            "question": "Is David Dhawan an actor or a director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5489171147346497,
            "question": "Can you give me another example of a film directed by David Dhawan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5243266224861145,
            "question": "What genre is the film Taaqatwar likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5027630925178528,
            "question": "Were there any famous actors in the film Taaqatwar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43134182691574097,
            "question": "Do you know of any awards or recognition received for the film Taaqatwar?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Dhawan directed the film Taaqatwar.",
            "html": "yago_10547_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any famous actors in the film Taaqatwar?",
            "html": "yago_10547_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Taaqatwar likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_10547_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give me another example of a film directed by David Dhawan?",
            "html": "yago_10547_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10547_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that David Dhawan made his directorial debut with the film Taaqatwar in 1989, which directly supports the statement that David Dhawan directed the film Taaqatwar."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}